tinierme.com 2011-12-04

# Privacy Policy | GCREST America Inc.

GCREST America, Inc. (" _Company_ ," “ _we_ ,” “ _our_ ” or “ _us_ ”) maintains this Privacy Policy (“ _Policy_ ") to explain to you how we collect, use and protect the privacy of all personal information gathered from customers, prospective customers, and visitors to our website(s), persons who download our products and services or otherwise access or use the GCREST America Online Entertainment services (the “Service”), which may be distributed through our website(s), third party website(s), third party social networking sites (“SNS”), directly to your mobile device or through such other applicable channel as may be applicable from time to time. This Policy also explains how you can review, update, correct, or delete your personal information and specify what information, if any, you would like to receive from us on an on-going basis.

* ##### 1\. Introduction

We are committed to ensuring your privacy and protecting the security of your personal information. This Policy covers all Services, including all of Company’s websites, online games, products, services and all online forms on our websites used to collect personal information. Please note that this Policy applies only to sites and content maintained by us or our affiliates, and not third party sites, whether linked to or from the Service. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. Moreover, this Policy does not apply to information collected by us offline. In addition, this Policy does not apply to other entities that we do not own or control or persons that are not our employees, agents or within our control. Note that you may also need to accept the Terms of Service and Privacy Policy of a third party social network sites if you access the Service from such an SNS.

By using or accessing the Service, or licensing and/or downloading any Company product or service, you are agreeing (i) to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Policy and represent that you have read and understood this Policy and (ii) that your access or use of the Service is subject to our [Terms of Service (" _TOS_ ")](http://www.gcrest.com/en/tos.php). If you do not understand or agree to be bound by (or cannot comply with) any terms or conditions described in this Policy, please exit from and do not access or use the Service. Your continued access of the Service or use, license and/or download of any of our products or services shall be deemed to constitute your agreement to be legally bound by this Policy and our [TOS](http://www.gcrest.com/en/tos.php), as they may be amended from time to time. Any references herein to “you” and “your” refers to both you and such person and entity on whose behalf you act, if any, and by accessing the Service, or using, licensing or downloading any of our products or services, you represent and warrant that you are authorized to bind such entity on whose behalf you act to the terms and conditions of this Policy.

* ##### 2\. Personal Information

You can access our Website without providing us with any personal information. However, Company may collect personal information in various locations on our Website as more particularly described below. Our primary goal in collecting the information described below is to provide you, the user, with a customized experience on our Website and to deliver better service, products, and more relevant content to our customers, prospective customers, and visitors. 

* ###### 2.1 Personal Information We Collect

Personal information may be collected from you during (a) the registration process (including inputting of your personal profile), (b) ordering and payment for products and services from the Service, or from and through third party service providers, (c) promotional campaigns or surveys, and/or (d) customer support and technical service inquiries, requests and notifications. Collected information may include your name, nickname, address, date of birth, gender, telephone, fax number, email address (including a friend’s email address when you make an introduction), physical address, website (if applicable), user ID, password, payment and billing information (including credit card number, expiry date, billing address, security code, etc.), and/or interests and preferences.

From time to time we may add to or change the information requested upon registration or log-in, so this may not be a complete list. We ask that you provide only your own personal information, not anyone else’s personal information. Personal information may be collected by Company and/or business partners such as co-sponsors.

* ###### 2.2 Cookies

"Cookies" are small strings of text that are sent to your computer by websites and are stored on your computer’s hard disk unless you set your browser to refuse them. We use cookies to optimize user identification functions and transmission of data. The information is collected on an aggregated and anonymous basis. Company also uses third party cookies in the following cases: (i) to measure the effectiveness of our online advertising; and (ii) to operate online games provided by other companies.  

Although you can set your browser to refuse cookies, doing so may affect your ability to use some of the features of the Service. For information about browser settings, please contact your browser’s software manufacturer. In some cases, companies that advertise within the Service may also use cookies in accordance with their own policies. 

* ###### 2.3 Log Files

Please also be aware that we collect log data such as your IP address and the like to analyze usage status and to improve and manage the services offered through the Service. We do not use log data to identify your personally identifiable information.

* ###### 2.4 Web Beacons

The Service may use a variety of methods for tracking purposes, including web beacons (also known as Internet tags, pixel tags and clear GIFs). Web beacons are small pieces of data that are embedded in images on the pages of websites to analyze traffic patterns, such as the frequency users visit various areas of the Service. These methods may involve transmitting information either directly to us or to another entity authorized by us to collect information on our behalf. We may also use these technical methods in HTML e-mails that we may send you to determine whether you have opened those e-mails or clicked on links in those e-mails. The information that we collect and share with web beacon technology is anonymous and not personally identifiable. It does not contain your name, address, telephone number, or email address. 

* ###### 2.5 Web Analytics Services

We may use certain web analytics services provided by third party vendors (collectively “ _Analytics Vendors_ ”). Such Analytics Vendors may use “cookies.” The information generated by the cookie about your use of certain websites relating to the Service (including your IP address) may be transmitted to and stored by the Analytics Vendors on servers in the United States or Japan. The Analytics Vendors will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of such websites, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. The Analytics Vendors may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on the Analytics Vendors’ behalf. The Analytics Vendors will not associate your IP address with any other data held by the Analytics Vendor. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of the Service. By accessing or using the Service, you consent to the processing of data about you by one or more Analytics Vendors in the manner and for the purposes set out above. 

* ##### 3\. Monitoring/Public Information

We often provide “profiles,” “chat,” “diaries,” “forums,” “blogs,” “mini-mail,” “recent visitors history,” “groups” and other similar features within the Service. You may choose to disclose personal information in such online chat rooms, blogs, bulletin boards, and/or other public forums (if any). Information appearing in these features may be viewed by anyone who uses the Service, and there is no expectation of privacy or confidentiality. We are not in any way liable for any damage you incur as a result of the appearance of your personal information in these features.

* ##### 4\. Use of Personal Information

Unless otherwise described elsewhere in this Policy, we will not disclose any of the personal information we collect from you or other visitors. 

* ###### 4.1 Use of Personal Information by Us

We use information you provide so that we may better understand your needs and the needs of other visitors. Specifically, we use your personal information for purposes including: 

  * (a) to allow you to register to use the Service, products and services;
  * (b) to allow you to apply for employment opportunities with us;
  * (c) to conduct quality control and ensure the smooth operation of the Service; 
  * (d) to analyze user characteristics and usage patterns in order to better understand how our products and the Service are used and market them more effectively;
  * (e) to communicate with you concerning your account(s) or to send you newsletters, surveys, contest and sweepstake announcements, and information about Service or product offerings or the offerings of our business partners; 
  * (f) to prevent or investigate actual or suspected fraud, hacking, infringement, or other misconduct involving our products and/or the Service; 
  * (g) to respond to inquiries, troubleshoot problems, investigate incidents, and handle complaints; and
  * (h) to develop new products and services.

* ###### 4.2 Sharing with Business Partners

We generally do not sell or trade any personal information about you to third parties. We may share, however, aggregated demographic information with our business partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. We may also disclose personal information to third party service providers, including those handling billing and payment settlement services, and system operations and management services. In such cases, we only disclose personal information necessary to carry out the delegated service and do not disclose any other information, and such third party service provides will be bound by confidentiality agreements restricting the use of any personal information for any purpose other than its intended use.

We may also periodically engage in co-marketing activities, where we work with a complementary solution provider to launch a joint marketing program. In these situations, we will only send information to you on behalf of the other; we do not provide your personal information to such partner. We may also enter into business partnerships with other parties to provide specific services. If you sign up for these services or responds to a particular marketing offer, we may share personal information such as your name or other contact information that is necessary for our business partner to provide these services or get in contact with you. 

Finally, in the event we combine with another company in the future through a corporate merger, sale, acquisition, liquidation or other similar process, your personal information may be transferred with the business or as a part of it, or may be sold as an asset of the business. 

* ##### 5\. Storage of Personal Information and Security

We take reasonable precaution to protect the personal information we collect from you and other visitors. When you submit personal information via the Service, the information is housed in a secure in-house database. In order to prevent unauthorized access, loss, or misuse, and to maintain data accuracy and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the personal information we maintain. We use industry-standard technology, such as firewalls, in an effort to protect the confidentiality of your personal information. Moreover, we encrypt your transmission of sensitive information to us (e.g., account passwords and payment-related identifiable information) via SSL (secured socket layer) protocol in the interest of heightened privacy protection and information integrity.

We also strive to ensure that your personal information is handled appropriately both internally and by service providers in accordance with rigorous information management practices, including restricting access rights, carrying out in-house training and educational activities, and carrying out necessary and appropriate supervision of service providers.

However, while we strive to protect your personal information, you should know that information sent over the Internet, whether by e-mail or by using one of our on-line forms, is not necessarily secure against interception. Therefore, we cannot and will not be responsible if your information is intercepted and cannot and do not guarantee the security of your information.

* ##### 6\. Opt-Out Provision

When we first collect information from you, we will offer you the opportunity to opt-out of having your personal information shared with third parties (unless otherwise described in this Policy). In addition, if you do not want us to send you e-mails or postal mail about our products and services, you can opt-out at the time of registration or information collection. If, at a later date, you choose to have your name or any other personal information removed from our mailing list, you can do so by emailing privacypolicy-usa@gcrest.com. 

* ##### 7\. California Privacy Rights

Residents of the State of California have the right to request from companies conducting business in California a list of all third parties to which the company has disclosed personal information during the preceding year for direct marketing purposes. Alternatively, the law provides that if the company has a privacy policy that gives either an opt-out or opt-in choice for use of your personal information by third parties (such as co-sponsors or advertisers) for marketing purposes, the company may instead provide you with information on how to exercise your disclosure choice options.

Company qualifies for the alternative option. We have a comprehensive privacy policy and provide you with details on how you may opt-out or opt-in to the use of your personal information by third parties for direct marketing purposes. Therefore, we are not required to maintain or disclose a list of the third parties that have received your personal information for marketing purposes during the preceding year. If you are a California resident and request information about how to exercise your third party disclosure choices you must send a request to privacypolicy-usa@gcrest.com. For such requests, you must put the statement “Privacy Policy Request” in the subject field of your email. For all requests, please include your name, street address, city, state, and zip code. Your street address is optional if you wish to receive a response to your request via email. Please include your zip code for our own recordkeeping. We will not accept requests via mail, telephone or by fax. We are not responsible for notices that are not labeled or sent properly, or do not have complete information.

* ##### 8\. Review, Update, Correct, or Delete Personal Information

Generally, you may review, update, correct or delete your personal information collected via the Service. You may also correct factual inaccuracies. Certain types of personal information that is necessary to check eligibility, such as birth date or age, cannot be deleted, but may be modified with sufficient verification of the new information. Note that we reserve the right to terminate or delete any registration or promotional entry if we believe the personal information submitted was knowingly false or fraudulent.

Depending on which Service your register for, Company may not be able to change registered information such as gender, nickname or user ID. If you wish to change these details, please re-register. Where applicable, you can change your email address, password, date of birth, and hometown by logging into the Service and changing your registered information and/or profile information on the settings page or equivalent. Unless otherwise described above, to review, update, correct or delete your personal information collected by the Service, please email us at privacypolicy-usa@gcrest.com. 

To have access to your personal information, you must provide proof of identification such as full name, street address, city/state and zip code, user ID and password, and/or information about your recent activity on the Service. We reserve the right to deny access to you if we believe there is a question about your identity. Moreover, we may still retain your information in our files to resolve disputes, enforce our [TOS](http://www.gcrest.com/en/tos.php), and for technical and legal requirements and constraints related to the Service. 

Please refer to our [TOS](http://www.gcrest.com/en/tos.php) for information on how to suspend or cancel registration and/or membership, or contact customer support for more information by emailing registration@tinierme.com. 

* ##### 9\. Legal Disclaimer

We may disclose personal information when required by law, regulation, court order, or in response to a subpoena or litigation discovery request, or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a legal process served on us.

* ##### 10\. Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our Policy, we will post those changes on our Policy page and/or within the relevant Service so you are aware of what personal information we collect from customers, prospective customers, and visitors to the Service, and when and how such information is collected, used and safeguarded. You are responsible for periodically checking for changes to this Policy. If at any time we decide to use personal information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will take commercially reasonable measures to notify you of such changes and/or obtain e-mail consent from you. If you do not consent to the usage of your personal information in that instance, you may refuse to use the Service at your discretion.

* ##### 11\. No Guarantees

While this Policy states our standards for maintenance of personal information and we will make efforts to meet them, we are not in a position to guarantee these standards. There may be factors beyond our control that may result in disclosure of personal information. As a consequence, we disclaim any warranties or representations relating to maintenance or nondisclosure of any personal information collected from you.

* ##### 12\. Links to Third Party Websites

The Service may contain links to external websites or other online content. Although these websites may have privacy policies, all of these websites and their privacy policies are independent of the Service and this Policy. We are not in any way involved in the handling of personally identifiable information on such other websites. We recommend that you confirm the privacy policies of the websites you visit if you leave the Service. 

* ##### 13\. Protection of Children’s Privacy

We are committed to providing special protection for the privacy of children who may visit the Service. We are also committed to fully complying with the U.S. Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act. We encourage parents to spend time online with their children, become familiar with the features of any and all of the Service or services that their child or children participate in, and participate in the activities offered on the Service. 

Our protections for the privacy of children include the following:

  * The Service is not directed to children under the age of 13. The Service prohibits registration by, and we will not knowingly collect, use or retain personally identifiable information from anyone under 13, for any purpose whatsoever (including internal or external marketing or promotional purposes). This requirement will be posted at points of data collection within the Service, such as registration for services. In addition, we will delete any records of such personal information that come to our attention.
  * Since we do not knowingly collect any personal information from visitors to the Service who are under 13, we do not knowingly disclose or transfer any such information to third parties. We do not request any visitor to provide any information about their family members, friends or other persons. 
  * We do not allow visitors who are under 13 to be listed in any directory of registered users, to participate in any of our chat services, to register for contests, sweepstakes, promotions, or newsletters, or to receive direct marketing from us or from our third-party affiliates or service or product providers.

* ###### 13.1 Special Note to Parents

If you become aware that your child has provided us with personal information via the Service, we invite you to notify us so that we may delete the information from our records and discontinue any related features or services (see Opt-Out Provision above). We also urge parents to instruct their children never to give out their real names, addresses or phone numbers without parental permission when using the Internet. We appreciate your cooperation in assisting us to provide a safe and enjoyable online experience for your children.

* ##### 14\. Governing Laws and Regulations

The Company is a U.S. company and Company’s business operations are primarily conducted in the State of California, U.S.A. We operate our company and administer this Policy under applicable U.S. and California laws and regulations. If you use the Service from outside United States, you are thereby consenting for your personal information to be processed in the United States in the manner described in this Policy. Furthermore, you acknowledge that the privacy laws of the United States and the State of California may differ from the laws in the state or country where you are located and may not provide you the same rights or protections as those laws.

* ##### 15\. Contact Us

If you have any questions, complaints, or comments regarding this Policy please contact us via e-mail at privacypolicy-usa@gcrest.com. If you have any other questions, please contact customer support at support@tinierme.com. 

Copyright © 2011 GCREST America, Inc. All rights reserved.
